Hello guys I'm ran Patrick bayas and I'm
my licensed financial advisor here in
manol philippines so For sure
you are looking for the cheapest term insurance that
you can add to your plan or
if what you are doing is a
btid strategy or by term invest the
difference so for SAO this video is
So you will know what is the
cheapest term insurance in the market
and as low as Php700 monthly How much is
the coverage so Let's take a look
So This is the term insurance
that I was talking about the name is manual
life React 5 this is a 5 year renewable and
convertible term insurance the good thing
here for now This is just
your budget but in the future I want to
have a whole life plan or vul plan
So you can invert it and convert it
Anytime without proof of insurability
meaning what was
your health condition when you took out the term
insurance or this manual life
React 5 this will be the basis of
your future plan if
you convert this plan and its renewal
is every 5 years meaning
its premium will only increase every 5 years  So is
that one of the good things about this plan?
Later you will see
what supplementary
benefits we can add to this
plan. So you will actually see the
premium or what
we will pay for the
plan. So this sample is the base
plan of manual life practice 5 or
our term insurance. So the profile of the
client that we put here for example
is male and 30 years old. So of course
it is health, so
our plan is just standard. So the minimum life
insurance is 1.5 million and then it
includes Accidental death and
total disability waiver which is a package in the
plan. So Accidental death
is also 1.5 million and then total
disability waiver. So we also know
the waiver if the Contra is every f years.
For example, the client is
paying for one year and is permanently
disabled. So the remaining 4 years of
life are yours. So think about it
at a price of 8.5 62 yearly or if
we divide that into 12, that's php7 122
only monthly. You have it.  of coverage of 1.5
million life insurance or total of 3
million protection with wave So if
you can see that, that's the
increase in the picture, the
payment crease, so every 5 years
only So if you want a big
plan coverage but
you'll only pay cheaply because
the whole life or vul plans don't fit into the budget
or you're doing the btid strategy, then
this term insurance is a good fit
So let's see how it would be if, for
example, you made it
comprehensive or you increased the
additional benefits or the
supplementary benefits of this plan, so let's
see So this is the
comprehensive term insurance or
manual life React 5, so
we added many supplementary benefits
and then at the same time we increased the
life insurance from 1.5 million to
2 million, so 2 million is the react Php5,
which is the equivalent of that, life
insurance 2 million and then Accidental
death benefit is 2 million So if the
client is not alive due to an accident, the total
that the family will get is 4 million, but
we also have the maximax plan 4 or this
maximax  plan for easy to say it's like a
personal accident anything related to an
accident like you're hospitalized
permanently disabled temporarily
disabled let's say you're six months You can't
work because
your foot is cemented or your arm is broken
you can receive allowances so
his Maxim Max plan
for Accidental insurance is great So if
for example the client dies in an
accident there is an additional 1 million from
maximax plan 4 so the maximax is pretty broad There are
so many benefits then
enhance critical illness Rider 160
critical illness Rider is now
its cover Of course the top
three stroke heart attack and then
cancer and then Of course it will not disappear Of course
only end stage disease chronic
kidney disease is included and then total
disability waiver so I mentioned
earlier what he is and then
our hospital income benefit is 1,000
per day then double it or 2,000 per
day if the dreaded disease is the cause of the
hospitalization or tripled or 3,000 per
per day if the client is confined to the ICU room
so that's just the basis of the hospital
income  1,000 we can do
4,000 5,000 10,000 then it will be doubled and
tripled so think about this
plan it's only more than Php2,000
its monthly if we divide it
Php25,000 is more than your coverage for
this plug so ' is the coverage so wide that
term insurance is not really necessary if your only purpose
is to be protected So if you want to
separate your investment you can
try to open a mutual fund uitf or if
others say they want
only mp2 or others are double
exploring btid or by term invest the
difference but mostly I advise
my client Um term insurance if it's
okay of course it's okay if
you bid if you have knowledge
about the and and then if you really want to go
to Manila so that you finish that
in 10 years e no You have a guaranteed
plan that will never disappear until h100 or
vul plan if you can consider  you or
the in I suggest term
insurance you can add on down to
your existing plans or you can also
just have this plan or you can just have this one
because it's the only one that
fits in the budget because it's cheap but
the coverage is great So that's all hopefully
you understand Ong manual life React
5 so again every 5 years I'm hoping so
ah and I forgot to say
renewable to until age 85 So until age
85 if the client is only 30 now
until age 85 he will be covered by this plan as long
as he renews So
anytime you can convert this term
insurance But sorry only until age 65 you
can convert so let's say
you thought about it at 40 convert to a whole
life plan to a compr comprehensive health
plan which is health flex or to a vul plan
or any plans you want endowment plan
so there are so many plans that can be
chosen here in Manal So that's all and
thank you for listening So if ah you have any
questions or you have inquiries or
you want a  sample quotation for your
age so just pm me sorry
just email me
the email is there in the description box and even
here in the video the phone number is also there
and then even
my Facebook account so that's all and thank you